<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>AI for Business on Camilo Rojas</title><link>https://camilorojas.co/posts/</link><description>Recent content in AI for Business on Camilo Rojas</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 20:12:44 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://camilorojas.co/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Convergence of market segments around AI</title><link>https://camilorojas.co/posts/convergence-ai/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 20:12:44 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://camilorojas.co/posts/convergence-ai/</guid><description>Chatbots, intelligent process automation, and generative AI are converging into an AI Agents stack. Here’s what’s driving the shift, who’s involved, and how to evaluate investments through a generative lens.</description></item><item><title>AI Catalogs: The Next Governance Artifact</title><link>https://camilorojas.co/posts/ai-catalogs/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 10:56:49 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://camilorojas.co/posts/ai-catalogs/</guid><description>Why AI catalogs are becoming the core enterprise artifact connecting gateways, governance, and security—plus a pragmatic path to get started.</description></item><item><title>The Evolution of AI Agent Development: From Complex Engineering to Accessible Tools</title><link>https://camilorojas.co/posts/building-agents/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 19:15:29 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://camilorojas.co/posts/building-agents/</guid><description>Exploring how AI agent development has evolved from requiring deep technical expertise to accessible no-code platforms, the emergence of domain-specific agents, and the critical role of industry standards in fostering innovation.</description></item><item><title>AI Agents: The Next Layer in Enterprise Architecture</title><link>https://camilorojas.co/posts/ai-agents/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2025 22:28:50 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://camilorojas.co/posts/ai-agents/</guid><description>AI Agents represent a fundamental shift in enterprise architecture, offering tool integration, memory persistence, and iterative reasoning. Based on hundreds of GenAI implementations, we explore two primary adoption patterns and their business impact.</description></item></channel></rss>